{
    "subject": "Jack_Norworth",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Louise_Dresser",
    "human_readable": "Jack Norworth is married to Louise Dresser.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9775430560112,
            "question": "Are Jack Norworth and Louise Dresser still married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9137674570083618,
            "question": "Can you tell me about the relationship between Jack Norworth and Louise Dresser?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.852339506149292,
            "question": "Who is married to Louise Dresser?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7109154462814331,
            "question": "Who is Jack Norworth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6891098022460938,
            "question": "Is Jack Norworth in a relationship?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6499301791191101,
            "question": "What is the name of Jack Norworth's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5254368782043457,
            "question": "What is Jack Norworth known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.494547039270401,
            "question": "What is Louise Dresser's marital status?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4676157236099243,
            "question": "What profession does Jack Norworth have?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.234991654753685,
            "question": "Is Louise Dresser a famous actress?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Jack Norworth is married to Louise Dresser.",
            "html": "yago_24377_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What profession does Jack Norworth have?",
            "html": "yago_24377_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Louise Dresser's marital status?",
            "html": "yago_24377_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Jack Norworth known for?",
            "html": "yago_24377_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24377_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24377_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24377_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24377_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24377_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24377_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24377_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24377_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24377_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24377_70.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the context information, the answer is:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`\n\nThis is because all the documents mention that Louise Dresser was previously married to Jack Norworth. \n\nDocument 3 specifically mentions that \"Dresser and Norworth were married from 1899 to 1908\".\n\nDocuments 4, 5, and 6 also confirm that Louise Dresser was married to Jack Norworth.\n\nTherefore, the triple \"Jack Norworth is married to Louise Dresser\" is supported by the information in the documents."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly indicate that Louise Dresser was previously married to Jack Norworth, supporting the statement that Jack Norworth was married to Louise Dresser."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}